sayshaadi.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy | SayShaadi | SayShaadi.com

This Privacy Policy covers SayShaadi.com, which shall be referred to as "we", "us", or "our" throughout this Privacy Policy. "You" as a user of SayShaadi.com, accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

In the course of providing wedding planning and other related services, we collect certain information from you. Our Privacy Policy describes the type of information we collect from you and what we do with that information.

##### Information 

In the course of registering for and availing various services we provide from time to time through our website www.SayShaadi.com ("Website", telephone search, SMS and WAP or any other medium in which SayShaadi may provide services ("Media") you may be required to give your Name, address, Email address, phone number.

The Personal Information is used for three general purposes: to customize the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain services, and to contact you about our services. Unless otherwise stated explicitly, this Policy applies to Personal Information as disclosed on any of the Media.

We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all Personal Information that you may share as a user of Media. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of organizations that we do not own or to people that we do not employ or manage.

##### Security 

Personal Information will be kept confidential and we do not disclose the information except that in case you are a customer of our search services through any of the Media. Further, the vendors / advertisers who are listed with us, may call you, based on the query or enquiry that you make with us, enquiring about any

Product / Service or

Product / Service of any subscriber / advertiser or

Product / Service of any particular subscriber / advertiser.

We will share Personal Information only under one or more of the following circumstances: - If we have your consent or deemed consent to do so - If we are compelled by law (including court orders) to do so.

In furtherance of the confidentiality with which we treat Personal Information we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We give you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time, including whether you want us to contact you regarding any services. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any registration process on our website or prior to availing of any services offered on our website if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you don't provide information that is requested it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail of the our services.

##### Contact us

If you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies; please send us an email at hi@SayShaadi.com

##### Links to other Websites

We have affiliate links to many other online resources. We are not responsible for the practices employed by these affiliates or their websites linked to or from SayShaadi.com nor the information or content contained on these third party websites. You should carefully review their privacy statements and other conditions of use and you agree you provide information or engage in transactions with these affiliates at your own risk. 

##### Updates on Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to revise these Privacy Policies of SayShaadi.com from time to time by updating this posting. Such revised policies will take effect as of the date of posting.
